Luis Fernandez Jr.

C: 863-521-6094 JrLuisFernandez@gmail.com www.LuisFernandezJr.com Winter Haven, FL

Information Technology Liaison | Security Data Analyst

Dedicated IT professional implementing, monitoring and administering IT systems. Project leader with experience in managing, mentoring, and motivating teams. Expertise in desktop and networks, data centers and analysis, cybersecurity and enterprise systems.

Technology Skills

Security: System Access Control, Vulnerability Scanning, Systems Administration

Systems: Windows, Unix, Linux, MacOS, iOS, Android, SQL, Oracle, Office 365

Programming: Python, XML, JavaScript, C, C++, , Go, Bash, , PHP, and HTML5

Networking: LANs, WANs, TCP / IP, VoIP, DNS, HTTPS, VPN, SFTP, Firewalls

Certifications: CompTIA A+ and Certified Ethical Hacking*

Professional Experience

Department of Transportation

Office Automation Specialist II Bartow, Florida Nov. 2018 – Present

Oversee trouble tickets. Deploys enterprise hardware and software. Ensures security and confidentiality across users and incidents. Utilizes SCCM, SharePoint, and Active Directory. Develop, apply, and provide documentation on technical policies and procedures.

- Liaison with engineers, consultants and staff in systems and applications
- Remote management of equipment with excellent customer service skills
- Technical resources responding to incidents, requests, and reporting

Polk State College

Data Analyst Winter Haven, Florida Jan. 2015 – Nov. 2018

Maintains, updates, implements and improves all software in Student Financial Services. Administer data security, security user roles, network drives, enterprise systems, SharePoint sites, and web portals. Compliance management in IBM Cognos, federal data and ERP systems.

- Manage and maintain data extracts to identify constraints, automate, and audit processes
- Advance the use of technology, projects, and research for improvement and development
- Report and reconcile millions of dollars in federal grants, loans, and scholarships

Polk State College

PC Support Specialist

Winter Haven, Florida

Jul. 2012 – Jan. 2015

Managed workstations, provided help desk and remote services across multiple sites and campuses. Setup servers, IT infrastructure, and provide service to all users. Scripted automatic installs of software. Oversee service tickets in Track-It Technician Client for improved SLA's.

- Utilize Active Directory and SCCM to manage group policy, accounts, and computers
- Provided Server support, Utilized Cisco Networking tools, and enterprise tools for issues

MF Electronics

Electronics Technician

Lake Hamilton, Florida

Jan. 2009 – Jun. 2012

Perform diagnostics on and deliver solutions to clients for TV sets, Computers, and other peripherals. Managed inventory of assets, provide invoices, and maintains orders with vendors.

- Lead point of contact in technical support and provided delivery of equipment
- Solder circuit boards, repair hardware, and provided warranties

Internships

SOFWERX

Data Science

Tampa, Florida

Jun. 2018 – Aug. 2018

Researched and implemented Data Science Methods and Development in Machine Learning. Utilization of Radio Frequency, Object Detection, Tensor Flow, Docker, and supporting API's.

Heart of Florida Regional Medical Center

Medical Information Systems

Davenport, Florida

Apr. 2008 – Sep. 2008

Assisted Networking Team and MIS Director with projects and tickets. Distributed RFID's access badges. Provide technical support in troubleshooting workstations and ticket escalation.

Education

University of South Florida

Master of Science, Cybersecurity, Cyber Intelligence

Aug. 2018

Polk State College

Bachelors of Applied Science, Supervision and Management, Business Admin.

Dec. 2017

University of South Florida

Bachelors of Applied Science, Information Technology

Aug. 2013